Register of the Victor Gilinsky Papers, 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- REACTOR SITES, 1974-1984
  - Diablo Canyon (California). Relates to seismic problems, construction reevaluation and safety studies. Reports, briefs, transcripts, correspondence, memoranda, clippings
    - 1981 Sept.-Oct. Relates to the re-evaluation of seismic design criteria, and whether these criteria (assuming they were correct) were properly applied in the case of Diablo Canyon (Box 367., Folder 1-9)
    - 1981 Oct.-Nov. Seismic design re-evaluation (Box 368., Folder 1-9)
    - 1981 Nov. Fuel loading and low power testing approval rescinded, Nov. 19; enforcement action considered (Box 369., Folder 1-8)
    - 1981 Dec. PG&E letter to the NRC describing commission of an independent seismic verification review study from R.L. Cloud Assoc., Inc. (Cloud study), Dec. 4 (Box 370., Folder 1-10)
    - 1981 Dec.-1982 Jan. Continuing review of ALAB-644, Dec. 18; investigation into the degree of involvement of PG&E in the Cloud study reports (Box 371., Folder 1-11)
    - 1982 Jan. NRC "Inspection Report of 'Preliminary Report, Seismic Verification Program' at Diablo Canyon Nuclear Power Plant, Units 1 and 2" Draft (Box 372., Folder 1-8)
    - 1982 Feb. NRC "Inspection Report of 'Preliminary Report, Seismic Verification Program' at Diablo Canyon Nuclear Power Plant, Units 1 and 2". Final report (Box 373., Folder 1-7)
    - 1982 Feb.-March. Includes statement by Dr. Gilinsky relating to the failure of the NRC to impose penalties for material false statements made by PG&E about the degree of independence of the Cloud study, Feb. 26 (Box 374., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 March-April. Continuing review of Cloud study; decision by the NRC to assign the Independent Design Verification Program (IDVP) to Teledyne Engineering Services, March 4; statement by Dr. Gilinksy on Commission review of ALAB-644, March 18; Bechtel Power Corp. hired by PG&E to assume the engineering management of Diablo Canyon, March 22 (Box 375., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 April-June. Includes IDVP reports (Box 376., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 June-Aug. Includes IDVP reports (Box 377., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 Aug.-Sept. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 378., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 Sept.-Oct. IDVP reports; PG&E final report on Phase I of its study, Oct. 1 (Box 379., Folder 1-8)
    - 1982 Nov. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 380., Folder 1-8)
    - 1982 Dec.-1983 Jan. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 381., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 Jan.-March. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 382., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 March-April. IDVP reports; Udall Committee hearing, March 8 (Box 383., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 April-May. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 384., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 May-June. Includes IDVP reports (Box 385., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 June. Numerous interim technical reports; first installments of Independent Design Verification Program final report, May 2 (Box 386., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 June-July. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 387., Folder 1-7)
    - 1983 July-Aug. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 388., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Aug. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 389., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 Aug.-Sept. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 390., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Sept. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 391., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 Sept.-Oct. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 392., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 Oct. Primarily IDVP reports (Box 393., Folder 1-7)
    - 1983 Oct. IDVP reports; discussion relating to lifting the license suspension; includes information on the "tau effect" (seismic safety factor) (Box 394., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Oct. IDVP reports; hearings, Oct. 28 (Box 395., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Nov.-Dec. Fuel loading approval granted, Nov. 8; includes a statement by Dr. Gilinsky (Box 396., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 Dec.-1984 Feb. NRC Safety Evaluation Report (SER), Supplement, relating to allegations, Dec. 23; IDVP reports (Box 397., Folder 1-11)
    - 1984 Feb. Includes material relating to the Quality Assurance program of Pullman Power Products and therefore the structural integrity of pipe welds, supports and restraints; Udall Committee hearing, Feb. 24 (Box 398., Folder 1-8)
    - 1984 March. Issues related to approval of low power testing, primarily continuing construction allegations and insufficient operator training and experience (Box 399., Folder 1-10)
    - 1984 March. Inspection reports relating to continuing allegations and low power testing (Box 400., Folder 1-9)
    - 1984 March-April. Inspection reports; "Table of Allegations Status", March 9; Gilinsky opinion, March 27; negative NRC inspection report presented by Isa Yin, March 26 meeting, and written report under April 3 cover memorandum (Box 401., Folder 1-7)
    - 1984 April. Advisory Committee on Reactor Safeguards (ACRS) meeting, April 6; low power approval, April 13 (Box 402., Folder 1-10)
    - 1984 April-May. Relates to emergency planning for earthquakes; includes transcript of a meeting between the NRC and PG&E about piping and piping support problems, May 9; enforcement action proposed, May 17 (Box 403., Folder 1-8)
    - 1984 May-June. IDVP report; Udall Committee hearings, June 14 (Box 404., Folder 1-6)
    - 1984 June. Includes further allegations (Box 405., Folder 1)
  - Dresden (Illinois). Relates to decontamination and other penalties and problems, 1980 Sept.-1983 March (Folder 2-4)
  - Erwin (Tennessee). Naval nuclear fuel manufacturing plant; relates to material accountability and security
    - 1982 Aug.-Dec. (Folder 5-10)
    - 1983 Jan.-June (Box 406., Folder 1-6)
  - Farley (Alabama). Relates to fuel loading and low power operating license proceedings
    - 1980 Aug. (Folder 7-8)
    - 1980 Sept.-1983 Aug. (Box 407., Folder 1-9)
  - Fitzpatrick (New York). Relates to allegations by the Union of Concerned Scientists regarding pipe supports, 1983 Sept. SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION/Siting/ Seismic issues/Large scale shutdown (Folder 10)
  - Fort St. Vrain (Colorado), 1978-1984. Release of radioactivity, 1978 Jan. 23; reactor scram, 1981 MAY 13 (Folder 11-12)
  - Ginna (New York)
    - 1982 Jan.-May. Steam generator tube rupture, 1982 Jan. 25 (Box 408., Folder 1-6)
    - 1982 May-1983 Oct. NRC reports on the accident and restart proceedings (Box 409., Folder 1)
  - Grand Gulf (Mississippi)
    - 1981 May-1982 Dec. Primarily construction and technical specifications; report on technical specifications, June 1982; site visit report and fuel loading and low power approval, 1982 June 16 (Folder 2-11)
    - 1983 Feb.-Dec. Safety Evaluation Report, 1983 May (Box 410., Folder 1-10)
    - 1984 Jan.-March. Relates primarily to amendments to technical specifications; includes computer printout and NRC status report of incidents at the plant, 1984 Feb.; continuing concerns about poor SALP ratings, errors in technical specifications, and operator inexperience; NRC meeting/status report, Feb. 29 (Box 411., Folder 1-9)
    - 1984 April. NRC meeting/technical specifications review, April 4 (Box 412., Folder 1-8)
    - 1984 April-May. Technical specifications review report submitted by Mississippi Power and Light, April 19; order restricting operation, April 24; letter/report to Rep. Edward Markey responding to his inquiry about problems with the plant, ca. May 4; order for inspection of TDI diesel generators, May 25 (Box 413., Folder 1-9)
    - 1984 June. Investigation report (Box 414., Folder 1-5)
  - Humboldt Bay (California), 1982 Sept.-Nov. (Folder 6)
  - Indian Point (New York). Relates generally to the re-evaluation of environmental and emergency contingencies due to the location of this reactor in a high-density population area, 1979 Dec.-1980 Dec.
    - General. Notebooks
      - Major Commission Decisions, 1980 May-1982 Sept. (Folder 7)
      - Review of ALAB-399
        - 1977 June-Oct. (Folder 8-12)
        - 1977 Oct.-1979 Jan. (Box 415., Folder 1-7)
      - Review of Union of Concerned Scientists (UCS) petition to revoke provisional operating license
        - 1979 Dec.-1980 Feb. (Folder 8-10)
        - 1980 April-1981 May (Box 416., Folder 1)
    - 1977 Sept.-1980 June. Report on effects of New York City blackout, 1977 Sept.; New York State Legislature Committee hearings, 1979 May; NRC Task Force report on interim operation, 1980 June 12 (Folder 2-11)
    - 1980 July-Dec. UCS petition denied, July 15; reactor trip and major leakage into containment facility, 1980 Oct. 17 (Box 417., Folder 1-8)
    - 1980 Dec.-1982 June. Investigation report, 1980 Dec. 10; Moffett Committee hearings, 1981 March 5; review of emergency preparedness plans, 1981 April; first emergency exercise, 1982 March 3 (Box 418., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 June-Aug. FEMA report, Aug. 2; Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, Aug. 16 (Box 419., Folder 1-11)
    - 1982 Aug.-Sept. Review of New York Port Authority safety study by Sandia Laboratories, Aug. 25 (Box 420., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 Sept.-Dec. Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, Sept. 24 and Oct. 1 (Box 421., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 Dec.-1983 March. Ottinger/Markey Committee hearing, March 1 (Box 422., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 March-May. Second full-scale emergency exercise, 1983 March 9; Federal Emergency Management Agency report, April 15; New York Port Authority report, May 3 (Box 423., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 May. NRC threatens to shut down the reactor if deficiencies are not corrected, May 5; oral presentations, May 26; New York State Disaster Preparedness Commission report, May 27 (Box 424., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 May-Oct. Shut down averted, June 10 (Box 425., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 Oct.-1984 April. ASLB report, 1983 Oct. 23; FEMA evaluation of ASLB report, 1984 Feb.; summary of ASLB report and responses, March (Box 426., Folder 1-7)
  - Kewaunee (Wisconsin), 1979 Jan.-Feb. Control rod malfunction, Jan. 10 (Folder 8)
  - Lacrosse (Wisconsin), 1981 May. Preliminary notification report relating to modifications of the containment structure (Folder 9)
  - La Salle (Illinois)
    - General. Safety Evaluation Report with Supplements, 1981 March-1983 Dec. (Box 427., Folder 1-4)
    - 1981 May-1982 June (Folder 5-8)
    - 1982 July. NRC investigation report, July 21; Government Accountability Project (GAP) report on allegations relating to the Zack Company (subcontractor for heating, ventilating and air conditioning equipment), 1982 July 27 (Box 428., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 Aug.-1984 March. Continuing quality assurance and safety inspections prior to full power decision, 1984 Feb.-March (Box 429., Folder 1-6)
  - Limerick (Pennsylvania)
    - 1980 Dec.-1983 Sept. Site visit, 1981 April 16 (Folder 7-11)
    - 1983 Oct.-1984 April. ACRS meeting transcript relating to emergency planning, 1983 Oct. 13; quality assurance allegations concerning welds (Box 430., Folder 1-6)
  - Maine Yankee (Maine), 1983 March-1984 April. Relates primarily to emergency planning. SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION/Siting/Seismic issues/Large scale shutdown (Folder 7-8)
  - Marble Hill (Indiana)
    - 1978 March. Relates to water discharge into the Ohio River (Folder 9)
    - 1978 April-1982 Jan.. Construction permit granted, 1978 April; shutdown due to quality assurance and managerial deficiences, 1979 Aug. (Box 431., Folder 1-7)
  - McGuire (North Carolina)
    - 1980 Aug.-1981 Jan. Notebook (Folder 8-9)
    - 1981 May-1983 May. NRC SER report, 1981 Jan.; ASLB authorizes operating license, 1981 May; briefing on full power license, May 27; full power approved, May 31 (Box 432., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 May. Briefing materials (Box 433., Folder 1)
  - Midland (Michigan)
    - 1981 Feb.-1983 March. Quality assurance problems and issues relating to the contruction of this plant on inadequately-consolidated fill soil; SER, 1982 Oct. (Folder 2-8)
    - 1983 April-June. Operating license hearing transcripts, June 1-3 (Box 434., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 June. Operating license hearing transcripts (contd.), June 4-10 (Box 435., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 June-July. Udall Committee hearing, June 16 (Box 436., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Aug.-1984 April. Continuing allegations and inspections (Box 437., Folder 1-5)
  - Nine Mile Point (New York), 1980 Nov.-1983 Oct. Inspection report, 1980 Nov.; enforcement actions, 1981 March 20 and Sept.4, 1983 April 26 and Oct. 7 (Folder 6-8)
    - 1975 June-1979 Dec. Enforcement action for construction violations, 1976 Dec.; allegations against the utility company (VEPCO) and the NRC relating to the construction of the plant on an earthquake fault, 1977 Sept.-Oct.; Hart/Simpson Committee hearing, 1977 Oct. 13; reactor trip and radiation release incident, 1979 Sept. 25 (Box 438., Folder 1-8)
    - 1980 Jan.-1983 Oct. SER, 1980 Aug.; full power license granted, 1980 Aug. 31 (Box 439., Folder 1-8)
  - Oconee (South Carolina), 1981 Aug.-1983 Aug. Enforcement action, 1982 June; steamline break incident, 1982 June 29. SEE ALSO: NRC TMI INVESTIGATIONS/Babcock & Wilcox/ General (Folder 9)
  - Oyster Creek (New Jersey), 1979 May-1983 Feb. Loss of feedwater incident, 1979 May 2; enforcement action, 1981 Aug.; NRC safety assessment report, 1982 Sept. (Box 440., Folder 1-3)
  - Palisades (Michigan), 1975 March-1983 Aug. Multiple incidents and enforcement actions: 1979 Nov. 9, 1981 Jan. 6 and Oct. 3, 1983 May 23 (Folder 4)
  - Palo Verde (Arizona), 1982 April-1983 Oct. Site visit, 1982 April 3-4; issues relating to full power license, 1983 March (Folder 5-7)
  - Peach Bottom (Pennsylvania), 1981 April-1983 June. Flooding incident, 1981 April 14; SALP report, 1982 March; other enforcement actions, 1983 March and June (Folder 8)
  - Pilgrim (Massachusetts), 1982 Jan. Enforcement action for multiple violations (Folder 9)
  - Pilgrim (Massachusetts), 1982 Jan.-June. Emergency planning (Box 441., Folder 1-4)
  - Point Beach (Wisconsin), 1979 Nov.-1983 Nov. Relates to problems with steam generator tube degradation; NRC inquiry report, 1980 May 8 (Folder 5-9)
  - Prairie Island (Minnesota), 1979 Oct.-1981 May. Steam generator tube failure, 1979 Oct. 2 (Folder 10)
  - Quad Cities (Illinois), 1984 Feb. Computer printouts of incident reports (Folder 11)
  - Rancho Seco (California), 1983 March-Nov. Relates primarily to post-TMI generic safety concerns. SEE ALSO: NRC TMI INVESTIGATIONS/Babcock & Wilcox/Rancho Seco/Brown, Gov. Edmund, Jr. (Folder 12)
  - St. Lucie (Florida)
    - General. SER with supplements, 1981 Oct.-1983 June (Box 442., Folder 1-3)
    - 1980 July-1981 Sept. Loss of coolant accident, reactor trip, 1980 June 11; NRC evaluation of incident, 1981 April 1 (Folder 4-8)
    - 1981 Oct.-1983 Aug. Fuel loading and low power approved, 1983 April 6; full power approved, 1983 June 10 (Box 443., Folder 1-3)
  - Salem (New Jersey)
    - General. Safety Evaluation Report, 1974 Oct. with supplements, 1976 Aug.-1980 April (Folder 4-9)
    - General. Supplements to SER, 1981 Jan.-May (Box 444., Folder 1)
    - 1980 April-Dec. Full power operating license review (Folder 2-9)
    - 1980 Dec.-1983 March. Full power license review (contd.); anticipated transient without scram events (ATWS), 1983 Feb. 23 and 25; NRC report entitled, "NRC Fact-finding Task Force Report on the ATWS Event at Salem Nuclear Generating Station, Unit 1, on Feb. 25, 1983" (Box 445., Folder 1-10)
    - 1983 March. Report (contd.); NRC meetings, March 2, 15 and 24 (Box 446., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 March-April. Udall Committee hearings, March 25; restart evaluation reports and meetings (Box 447., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 April-July. NRC report on the generic implications of the ATWS events (draft and final copies); responses to an inquiry by Senator Joseph Biden, June 2; management assessment and action plan submitted by the utility, June 24 (Box 448., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 July-1984 June. Enforcement action and continuing NRC review; SALP, Nov. 7 (Box 449., Folder 1-4)
  - San Onofre (California)
    - General
      - General, 1982 July-1983 Aug. Notebook relating to concerns over depressurization systems in the event of loss of coolant accidents such as a steam tube rupture (Folder 5-6)
      - Safety Evaluation Report, 1981 Jan. (Folder 7)
      - Safety Evaluation Report (Supplements 1-6), 1981 Feb.-1982 June (Box 450., Folder 1-2)
    - 1981 July-1982 Jan. Emergency planning relating to earthquakes, FEMA report, Dec. 1; approval for fuel loading and low power operation, Jan. 11; design verification study program plan study submitted, Jan. 22 (Folder 3-8)
    - 1982 Feb.-July. ASLB decision on emergency planning issues, May 14; enforcement action related to physical security violations, June 14; materials relating to full power approval (Box 451., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 Aug.-1983 Sept. Approval of full power license for Unit 2, 1982 Sept. 7; reactor trip incident, 1982 Nov. 10; amendment to operating license and continuing allegations, 1983; NRC evaluation of the PORV/pressurizer system, 1983 Sept. 15 (Box 452., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Sept.-Nov. Full power license approved for Unit 3, Sept. 19 (Box 453., Folder 1)
  - Seabrook (New Hampshire)
    - 1981 Feb.-1984 April. Site visit, 1983 Aug. 19 (Folder 2-11)
    - 1984 April-May. Design inspection report, 1984 April 2 (Box 454., Folder 1)
  - Sequoyah (Tennessee). SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR SAFETY AND RESEARCH/Specific problems/Hydrogen control
    - General. Collected materials relating to problems with welding repairs and tests of pressurizer relief lines, 1980 July-1981 Feb. (Folder 2-5)
    - 1979 Dec.-July 1980. Relates to fuel loading and low power licensing proceedings, emergency planning, and the ice containment system; site visit, June 22-23 (Folder 6-10)
    - 1980 Aug. Full power licensing proceedings (Box 455., Folder 1-11)
    - 1980 Sept.-1984 Feb. SER, 1980 Aug.; full power license for Unit 1 approved, 1980 Sept. 17; full power license for Unit 2 approved, 1981 Sept. 16; SER relating to the containment issue with cover memorandum, 1982 Dec. (Box 456., Folder 1-9)
  - Shearon Harris (North Carolina), 1978 Aug.-1981 Nov. Report on investigation of allegations, 1978 Nov. (Box 457., Folder 1-10)
  - Shoreham (New York)
    - 1981 Oct.-1983 April. Relates to attempts by Suffolk County to block the plant by refusing to develop an emergency evacuation plan (Box 458., Folder 1-10)
    - 1983 May-Sept. ASLB Partial Initial Decision covering most issues related to Shoreham except emergency planning and allegations of problems with diesel generators, Sept. 21 (Box 459., Folder 1-6)
    - 1983 Sept.-1984 April. Unpublished appendices to ASLB decision report, Sept; FEMA report, March 15; SER supplement, April (Box 460., Folder 1-8)
    - 1984 April-May. Report on failure of emergency diesel generator, May 9; Udall Committee hearing, May 17 (Box 461., Folder 1-9)
    - 1984 May-June. Primarily material relating to a motion by Suffolk County to disqualify Chairman Palladino and three administrative judges (Box 462., Folder 1-5)
    - 1980 April-Sept. Draft investigation report relating to the effectiveness of quality assurance programs, April 11; enforcement action, April 29 (Folder 6-10)
    - 1980 Sept.-1981 Oct. Dept. of Justice decides not to initiate criminal prosecution, 1981 June; investigation report, Oct. 10 (Box 463., Folder 1-10)
    - 1981 Nov.-1984 April.; design review reporting significant health and safety problems, 1981 Nov. 16; ASLB Partial Initial Decision on license, 1984 March 14 (Box 464., Folder 1-10)
  - Stanislaus (California), 1981 Dec. and 1983 March. Primarily "Petition to Enforce and Modify License Conditions". Relates to an agreement for a proposed transmission interconnection between North California Power Agency's geothermal project and PG&E (Box 465., Folder 1-9)
    - General. Antitrust action within utility cooperative, 1980 May-1981 June (Folder 10-12)
    - 1980 Nov.-1982 June. Emergency exercise, 1981 April 13 (Box 466., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 June-1983 March. Site visit, June 23; report on seismic design and piping systems, 1982 Oct.; full power deliberations, 1982 Nov. (Box 467., Folder 1-11)
  - Surry (Virginia), 1980 July-1983 May. Investigation report on multiple allegations relating to operational and security violations, 1980 July; enforcement action, 1983 May 9. SEE ALSO: NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION/ Siting/Seismic issues/Large scale shutdown (Box 468., Folder 1-2)
  - Susquehanna (Pennsylvania)
    - General. Safety Evaluation Report (with Supplements), 1981 April-1984 March (Folder 3-6)
    - 1982 April. ASLB approval for licensing (Folder 7)
    - 1982 May-Nov. Includes materials relating to the containment system and welds; low power approval, July 19; Teledyne design review report, Aug. 23 (with addendum, Oct.); site visit, Sept. 13; investigation pending, Oct.; full power approval, Nov. 15 (Box 469., Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 March-1984 May. Materials relating to FBI investigation and NRC enforcement action, 1983 March-April; SER Supplement and discussion relating to full power approval for Unit 2, 1984 May (Box 470., Folder 1-3)
  - Turkey Point (Florida), 1981 Feb.-1983 Aug. Enforcement actions, 1981 Feb. 18 and 1983 Aug. 16 (Folder 4)
  - Vermont Yankee (Vermont), 1981 Sept.-1983 Aug. Management performance appraisal report, 1981 Sept. 9; site visit, 1982 Feb. 17; emergency exercise, 1982 Feb. 18; enforcement actions, 1982 Oct. 15 and 1983 May 11 (Folder 5)
  - Washington Public Power Supply System (WPPSS) (Folder 6-8)
    - General. SER and Supplements, 1982 March-1983 Dec.
    - 1979 Oct.-1984 April. Investigation of allegedly falsified welding records, 1979 Oct.-Dec.; site visit, 1982 Dec. 2; materials relating to full power approval for Unit 2, including SER Supplement #5 and a quality assurance construction report, 1984 March 29 (Box 471., Folder 1-5)
  - Waterford (Louisiana), 1981 June-1983 Dec. Site visit, 1983 March 9; enforcement action, 1983 March 16; allegations relating to deficiencies in quality assurance program, 1983 April-June (Folder 6-9)
  - Zimmer (Ohio)
    - General. Allegations by Thomas Applegate
      - 1982 July-1983 Feb. Letter from Thomas Applegate alleging NRC misconduct in the Zimmer investigation, 1982 July/Aug. (?) 16; NRC interview report, Nov. 16; inquiry from Rep. Morris Udall, Dec. 7; NRC draft responses to the Udall letter, 1983 Jan.-Feb.; Applegate v. NRC decision relating to the release of documents, 1983 Jan. 18 (Folder 10-11)
      - 1983 March-1983 Aug. Investigation of NRC investigation of Applegate allegations: NRC meetings, June 16, 17 and 20 and Aug. 3; Hoyt-Aloot report (two annotated copies), July 12 (Box 472., Folder 1-11)
      - 1983 Aug.-1984 Feb. NRC reports, Aug. 31 and Oct. 12; NRC meetings, Oct. 7 and Dec. 5; NRC statement, Oct. 28; affidavit by James Cummings, Jan. 27 (Box 473., Folder 1-8)
    - 1981 April-Aug. NRC investigation report, Aug. 7. NOTE: the following categories also include materials relating to allegations (Folder 9-11)
    - 1981 Aug.-Oct. NRC investigation report, Oct. 16 (Box 474., Folder 1-11)
    - 1981 Nov.-1982 July. Final of NRC investigation report, Oct. 16; site visit, April 26-27; NRC meeting, May 26; site visit report, June; Udall Committee hearing, June 10; NRC meeting, June 16 (Box 475., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 July-Aug. Includes weld documents relating to allegations (Box 476., Folder 1-10)
    - 1982 Sept.-Oct. Udall Committee hearing, Sept. 14 (Box 477., Folder 1-9)
    - 1982 Oct.-1983 Jan. Briefing materials, Oct. 28; NRC order to halt construction due to multiple problems, Nov. 12 (Box 478., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Jan.-April. NRC public meeting, Jan. 5; NRC investigation report, Jan. 17; controversy over suggestion that Bechtel Power Corp. perform the independent management review required by the NRC in the 1982 Nov. 12 order--Torrey Pines Technology chosen instead (Box 479., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 April-July. NRC report on construction quality, April (Box 480., Folder 1-9)